Rushi Mashru

Full Stack Engineer

8.0+ years experienced and awarded full-stack engineer, strong and diverse experience working with Azure Services, MVC .Net 6, Azure Al/ML Services, Python, JavaScript, ReactJS, and MS SQL Server. Enthusiastic proactive natural learner with a flair to learn new technologies and design solutions, looking to secure a challenging position where I can effectively contribute my strong technical skills.

rushi.p.mashru@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/rushimashru



github.com/RushiMashru

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Software Engineer

Harman (A Samsung company)

07/2022 - Present Bengaluru, IN Harman Connected Services is a subsidiary of Samsung Electronics Roles & Responsibility

- AI Engineer: Developed (AI) FAQ solution for client using Azure language service, developed solution for feedback analysis using azure cognitive services.
- Back-end Engineer: Developed microservices and REST API, using .Net 6 and Azure services.
- Build data transformation pipelines using Azure Data Factory.

Solution Engineer - AI CoE Deloitte

01/2019 - 07/2022 Hvderabad, IN Deloitte is one of the "Big Four" accounting organizations Roles & Responsibility

• Al-ML Engineer: Worked on Azure Al services, Azure ML services, and python based ML libraries.

Software Engineer

Gateway Technolabs

01/2018 - 12/2018 IT Consultancy and Services Ahmedabad, IN

Roles & Responsibility

• Full Stack Developer: Developed e-commerce web app for Automobile Industry, using ReactJS & REST API

Software Engineer The One Technologies

07/2016 - 01/2018

Ahmedabad, IN

Startup, IT consultancy and services

Roles & Responsibility

 Full Stack Developer: Worked on MVC .Net, REST API, jQuery, HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS3 and MS SQL Server

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering

AITS, Gujarat Technological University

04/2012 - 06/2016

Gujarat, India

 Computer Engineering, 8.0/10.0 GPA

• GPA (World Education Service Certified): 3.6 / 4

HSC (Science)

St. Mary's School, Porbandar

03/2010 - 04/2012

PRIMARY SKILLS

Microsoft Full Stack Engineer

Azure AI/ML Engineer

AWARDS

Spot Award - Q3 2019 | Q2 2021 | Q3 2021 | Q1 2022 Deloitte.

Spark Award - Q2 2018

Gateway Technolabs

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Artificial Intelligence

 Azure Cognitive Services, Azure Al Custom Vision Services, Azure ML Studio, Azure ML SDK, Python based ML and NLP using libraries like pandas, sklearn, nltk, scipy, spacy, openCV and seaborn

Azure Services

 Web App Services, Azure Functions, Azure Service Bus, Cosmos DB, Azure API Management, Storage Services, Azure SQL, Azure Data Factory, Azure Key Vault and Azure Application Insights

Microsoft Technologies

º C#, .Net 6, .Net Core, MVC 5, REST API, MS SQL Server

Web Development Technologies

JavaScript, jQuery, ReactJS, Bootstrap, HTML 5

CERTIFICATES

AI-102 Microsoft Certified: Azure Al Engineer Associate (09/2021)

DP-100 Microsoft Certified: Azure Data Scientist Associate (12/2021)

AI-900 Microsoft Certified: Azure Al Fundamentals (06/2021)

AZ-204: Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure (12/2022)

AZ-900 Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (06/2021)

DP-900: Azure Data Fundamentals (01/2023)

DP-420: Azure Cosmos DB Developer Specialty (09/2024)